Cotton or plastic: which kind of bag is better for the environment?
棉质还是塑料：哪种袋子对环境更好？
Many of us would naturally say that the cotton bag is best, but that might only be true if you use that bag thousands of times.
我们很多人自然会说是棉布袋最好，可能确实如此，但前提是你使用那个袋子数千次。
Surprised?
感到惊讶吗？
Keep listening and we'll explain.
继续听，我们会解释。
There is no doubt that plastic is damaging for the environment in many ways.
毫无疑问，塑料在许多方面对环境都有害。
Producing it can cause toxins to be released into the atmosphere.
生产塑料会导致毒素释放到大气中。
It's used in great quantities and often disposed of after a single use, meaning even more then needs to be produced.
塑料的使用量巨大，且常在被一次性使用后就丢弃，这意味着需要生产更多的塑料。
Thrown-away plastic can sit in landfill sites for centuries, or alternatively can contaminate the sea causing harm to wildlife and breaking down into polluting microplastics.
被丢弃的塑料可以在垃圾填埋场中存留数个世纪，或者污染海洋，危害野生动物，并分解成污染性的微塑料。
Because of these factors, many people are looking for ways to reduce their plastic use.
由于这些因素，许多人正在寻找减少塑料使用的方法。
However, the picture is not straightforward.
然而，情况并非那么简单。
Let's return to our cotton bag.
让我们回到棉布袋。
It's certainly more biodegradable than plastic, but this might be where the advantages end.
它当然比塑料更可生物降解，但这可能也是它仅有的优点。
The industrial production of cotton requires far more energy, along with water and pesticides.
棉花的工业生产需要更多的能源，以及水和杀虫剂。
As the bags are heavier, transporting them will lead to higher carbon emissions.
由于袋子更重，运输它们将导致更高的碳排放。
An article from Columbia University suggests that cotton shopping bags need to be used over 7,000 times before they are more sustainable than plastic ones.
哥伦比亚大学的一篇文章表明，棉质购物袋需要被使用超过7000次，才能比塑料袋更可持续。
It's not just about shopping bags.
这不仅仅是购物袋的问题。
Lightweight plastic components in cars and planes help reduce fuel use and emissions.
汽车和飞机中的轻质塑料部件有助于减少燃料使用和排放。
If we didn't use so much plastic in clothing and footwear, the amount of land, water and chemicals that would be needed to produce enough natural textiles and leather would be enormous.
如果我们不在服装和鞋类中使用这么多塑料，那么生产足够的天然纺织品和皮革所需的土地、水和化学品将是巨大的。
Researchers have been looking to see if carbon could be sequestered during the production of plastics, reducing the amount in the atmosphere.
研究人员一直在探索是否可以在塑料生产过程中封存碳，从而减少大气中的碳含量。
One other characteristic of plastic might actually be the key to this issue.
塑料的另一个特性实际上可能是这个问题的关键。
The fact that plastic lasts for centuries is what causes much of the environmental harm, but it also means it can be used to make items that can be re-used again and again.
塑料能持续存在数百年这一事实造成了大部分环境危害，但这也意味着它可以被用来制造可以被反复使用的物品。
The problem is that we often don't.
问题在于我们往往不这样做。
Plastic can cause serious harm to the environment, and efforts to throw less of it away can reduce this.
塑料会对环境造成严重危害，而努力少丢弃一些塑料可以减少这种危害。
Re-using it more could be one way to achieve this.
更多地重复使用塑料是实现这一目标的一种方式。